<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="0.91">
	<channel>
		<title>WriteTheWeb</title> 
		<link>http://writetheweb.com</link> 
		<description>News for web users that write back</description> 
		<language>en-us</language> 
		<copyright>Copyright 2000, WriteTheWeb team.</copyright> 
		<managingEditor>editor@writetheweb.com</managingEditor> 
		<webMaster>webmaster@writetheweb.com</webMaster> 
		<image>
			<title>WriteTheWeb</title> 
			<url>http://writetheweb.com/images/mynetscape88.gif</url> 
			<link>http://writetheweb.com</link> 
			<width>88</width> 
			<height>31</height> 
			<description>News for web users that write back</description> 
			</image>
		<item>
			<title>Giving the world a pluggable Gnutella</title> 
			<link>http://writetheweb.com/read.php?item=24</link> 
			<description>WorldOS is a framework on which to build programs that work like Freenet or Gnutella -allowing distributed applications using peer-to-peer routing.</description> 
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Syndication discussions hot up</title> 
			<link>http://writetheweb.com/read.php?item=23</link> 
			<description>After a period of dormancy, the Syndication mailing list has become active again, with contributions from leaders in traditional media and Web syndication.</description> 
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Personal web server integrates file sharing and messaging</title> 
			<link>http://writetheweb.com/read.php?item=22</link> 
			<description>The Magi Project is an innovative project to create a combined personal web server and messaging system that enables the sharing and synchronization of information across desktop, laptop and palmtop devices.</description> 
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Syndication and Metadata</title> 
			<link>http://writetheweb.com/read.php?item=21</link> 
			<description>RSS is probably the best known metadata format around. RDF is probably one of the least understood. In this essay, published on my O'Reilly Network weblog, I argue that the next generation of RSS should be based on RDF.</description> 
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>UK bloggers get organised</title> 
			<link>http://writetheweb.com/read.php?item=20</link> 
			<description>Looks like the weblogs scene is gathering pace beyond the shores of the US. There's now a UK-specific page on weblogs.com, and a mailing list at egroups.</description> 
			</item>
		<item>
			<title>Yournamehere.com more important than anything</title> 
			<link>http://writetheweb.com/read.php?item=19</link> 
			<description>Whatever you're publishing on the web, your site name is the most valuable asset you have, according to Carl Steadman.</description> 
			</item>
		</channel>
	</rss>
